<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hamid&#39; blog</title>
    <link>adibzadeh.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hamid&#39; blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0330</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="adibzadeh.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Slower</title>
      <link>adibzadeh.github.io/lifestyle/slower/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 13:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adibzadeh.github.io/lifestyle/slower/</guid>
      <description>I often look at time as something fast. Things happen in the blink of an eye. Different situations form in front of you and then disappear regardless of how you react to them.
But, a few days ago, for a moment, I felt it is also really slow. And it gets slower when you limit your thoughts and actions. You feel you have more space, and you can breathe. In other words, the amount of “things” you do and think about, has a direct effect on your feeling of the speed of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Springtime</title>
      <link>adibzadeh.github.io/general/springtime/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 14:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adibzadeh.github.io/general/springtime/</guid>
      <description>I’m glad that springtimeis coming.
Spring is good and refreshing. I believe everything about it is very standard and normal. Although Summer is still my favorite season, Spring is the second one. And there is one small reason for it called “Hope”. I feel It’s like the planet wakes up after weeks of hard and cold days. And you can see it’s still hopeful, green and fresh!
Also, Spring is the start of a new Iranian year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Walking</title>
      <link>adibzadeh.github.io/lifestyle/about-walking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 14:50:00 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adibzadeh.github.io/lifestyle/about-walking/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to walking as exercise, most of us just assume we know it all and move on. But, do we?
This post is a little different. I wanna talk about my experience.
In my whole life so far, I always struggled and had difficult times dealing with my mental health and my mood stability. From normal daily life activities to working as a professional programmer. Over the past few years, I studied a lot hoping to find a way to help myself build the life I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi</title>
      <link>adibzadeh.github.io/general/hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Mar 2021 15:47:24 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>adibzadeh.github.io/general/hi/</guid>
      <description>Hi, Welcome to my blog.
Enjoy the silence in this empty and quiet post until I share more thoughts! :)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>